meundies.com 2019-12-09

# MeUndies | The World's Most Comfortable Underwear for Men & Women - MeUndies

Last Updated: May 25, 2018 

MeUndies Inc. (" **MeUndies** ") is committed to protecting your privacy. We have prepared this Privacy Policy to describe to you our practices regarding the Personal Data (as defined below) we collect from users of our website located at [www.meundies.com](https://www.meundies.com/) (the " **Site** ") and our online services (" **Services** "). We have prepared this Privacy Policy to describe to you our own practices regarding the Personal Data (as defined below) that we collect from our Site and Services. 

##  1\. Questions; Contacting MeUndies; Reporting Violations. 

If you have any questions or concerns or complaints about our Privacy Policy or our data collection or processing practices, or if you want to report any suspected security violations to us, please contact us at the following: 

MeUndies Inc.   
c/o TJ Stein   
3650 Holdrege Ave, Los Angeles, CA 90016   

##  2\. User Consent. 

By visiting our Site, using our Services, or providing us with your Personal Data through our Site or Services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

##  3\. A Note About Children. 

We do not intentionally gather Personal Data from visitors who are under the age of 13. If we discover that a child under 13 has submitted Personal Data to MeUndies, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible. If you believe that we might have any Personal Data from a child under 13, please contact us at [abuse@meundies.com](mailto:abuse@meundies.com)

##  4\. A Note to Users Outside of the United States. 

**Your Personal Data may be processed in the country in which it was collected and in other countries, including the United States, where laws regarding the processing of Personal Data may be less protective than the laws in your country. By providing your data, you consent to such processing and transfer.**

##  5\. Types of Data We Collect. 

" **Personal Data** " means data that, by itself, allows someone to identify or contact you as an individual, including, for example, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, as well as any other non-public information about you that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing data. " **Anonymous Data** " means data that does not, by itself, permit the identification of individual persons and that is not associated with or linked to Personal Data. We collect Personal Data and Anonymous Data, as described below. 

  1. ###  Information You Provide to Us. 

    * We may collect your e-mail address and password when you create an account to log in to our network (" **Account** "). 
    * When you order products or gift cards on our Site, we will collect all information necessary to complete the transaction, including your name, credit card information, billing information, and shipping address information. 
    * If you subscribe to our e-mail newsletter, we will collect your e-mail address. 
    * If you provide us feedback or contact us via e-mail, we will collect your name and e-mail address, as well as any other content included in your e-mail to us, in order to send you a reply. 
    * We may also collect Personal Data at other points in our Site or Services that state that Personal Data is being collected. 
  2. ###  Information You Provide to Social Networking Sites. 

If you elect to sign in to your Account via a social networking site (" **SNS** "), you are allowing us to access information stored by the SNS, including, without limitation, information in your public profile and your email address, and you are agreeing to the SNS’s terms of use in your use of the Services. We may receive information from the SNS to make it easier for you to create an Account on the Site and provide you with relevant content. Any information that we collect from your SNS account may depend on the privacy settings you have selected with that SNS, so please consult the SNS’s privacy policy and data practices. 

  3. ###  Information Collected via Technology. 

    * Information Collected by Our Servers. 

To make our Site and Services more useful to you, our servers (which may be hosted by a third-party service provider) may collect information from your computer or device, including but not limited to: 

      * The date and time of your visit and the web pages and content you view and links you click on while navigating within our Services; 
      * Information about the type of content accessed via our Services; 
      * The site you visited before and after visiting our Site; 
      * Your Internet Protocol (IP) address (a numerical address assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider so that other computers connected to the Internet can communicate with your browser online) that can sometimes be used to derive your general geographic area; 
      * Search terms you enter using our Services or on a referral site; 
      * Unique identifiers, including non-global mobile device identification numbers; 
      * Information about your device such as your device type, screen size, browser type, language and other settings, memory capacity, plug-ins, Internet domain, TCP configuration parameters, operating system, carrier code, time zone and the names, versions and package IDs of software installed on your device; and 
      * Information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other tracking technologies (see additional descriptions of these terms below). 
    * Cookies. 

Like many online services, we use cookies to collect information. " **Cookies** " are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing the website. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Site and Services. 

    * Pixel Tags. 

In addition, we use " **Pixel Tags** " (also referred to as clear Gifs, Web beacons, or Web bugs). Pixel Tags are tiny graphic images with a unique identifier, similar in function to Cookies, that are used to track online movements of Web users. In contrast to Cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, Pixel Tags are embedded invisibly in Web pages and e-mail messages. We may use Pixel Tags to collect information about your interactions with our email messages, such as the links you click on and whether you open or forward a message, the date and time of these interactions and the device you use to read emails. 

    * Do Not Track. 

We do not currently respond to "do not track" signals from web browsers. 

    * Analytics Services. 

We use third-party analytics services (" **Analytics Services** "), to help analyze how users use our Site. The information generated by the Cookies or other technologies about your use of our Site (the " **Analytics Information** ") is transmitted to the Analytics Services. The Analytics Services use Analytics Information to compile reports on user activity. The Analytics Services may also transfer the Analytics Information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process Analytics Information on their behalf. Each Analytics Service’s ability to use and share Analytics Information is restricted by such Analytics Service’s terms of use and privacy policy. By using our Site, you consent to the processing of data about you by Analytics Services in the manner and for the purposes set out above. For a full list of Analytics Services, please contact us at [support@meundies.com](mailto:support@meundies.com)

  4. ###  Information Collected from You About Others. 

    * If you send a gift card to a third party, we will collect both your and the third party’s name and e-mail address in order to send the third party an electronic gift card. 
    * If you decide to invite a third party to purchase our products, we will collect your and the third party’s name, e-mail address, and/or social media account username in order to send a promotional message to the third party. We rely upon you to obtain whatever consents from the third party that may be required by law to allow us to contact the third party. You or the third party may contact us at [support@meundies.com](mailto:support@meundies.com) to request the removal of this information from our database. To make the referral process easier, we provide you the opportunity to import contact information directly from your address book. With your permission, we will access your address book and import your contacts’ information to facilitate the referral process. The communication that is sent to your friends may come from your e-mail address or social media account so that your friends know that you want to invite them to visit our Site. 

##  6\. Use of Your Personal Data 

  1. ###  General Use. 

In general, Personal Data you submit to us is used either to respond to requests that you make or to aid us in serving you better. We and our authorized service providers may use your Personal Data in various ways, including to: 

    * facilitate the creation of and secure your Account on our network; 
    * identify you as a user in our system; 
    * provide improved administration of our Site and Services; 
    * provide the products and Services you request; 
    * measure and analyze audience traffic and improve the quality of your experience when you interact with our Site and Services; 
    * send you a welcome e-mail to verify ownership of the e-mail address provided when your Account was created; 
    * send you administrative e-mail notifications, such as security, or support and maintenance advisories; 
    * respond to your inquiries related to employment opportunities or other requests; 
    * send newsletters, surveys, offers, and other promotional materials and for other marketing purposes; 
    * help recognize you as a previous visitor and save and remember your preferences and settings and deliver to you appropriate interest-based content; 
    * understand whether our users read email messages and click on links within those messages; 
    * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, comply with applicable law and enforce our Terms of Service; and 
    * for any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect your information or pursuant to your consent. 
  2. ###  User Testimonials. 

We often receive testimonials and comments from users who have had positive experiences with our products and Services. We occasionally publish such content. When we publish this content, we may identify our users by their social media account usernames and publish their social media account profile pictures. 

  3. ###  Creation of Anonymous Data. 

We may create Anonymous Data records from Personal Data by excluding information (such as your name) that makes the data personally identifiable to you. We reserve the right to use Anonymous Data for any purpose and disclose Anonymous Data to third parties in our sole discretion. 

##  7\. Disclosure of Your Personal Data. 

We disclose your Personal Data as described below and as described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy. 

  1. ###  Third-Party Service Providers. 

We may share your Personal Data with payment processors and other third-party service providers that assist us in the operation of our services as needed to fulfill your orders, conduct quality assurance testing, facilitate creation of accounts, provide technical support; and/or provide other services to MeUndies. For example, MeUndies has implemented a Google Maps API Implementation within the Site. Your use of the Site is subject to, and MeUndies hereby incorporates by reference, [Google’s Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy) as such policy may be amended by Google from time to time. 

  2. ###  Affiliates. 

We may share some or all of your Personal Data with our parent company, subsidiaries, joint venturers, or other companies under common control with MeUndies ("Affiliates"), in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. 

  3. ###  Corporate Restructuring. 

We may share some or all of your Personal Data in connection with or during negotiation of any merger, financing, acquisition or dissolution transaction or proceeding involving the sale, transfer, or divestiture of all or a portion of our business or assets. In the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, Personal Data may also be transferred as a business asset. If another company acquires our company, business, or assets, that company will possess the Personal Data collected by us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy. 

  4. ###  Other Disclosures. 

Regardless of any choices you make regarding your Personal Data (as described below), MeUndies may disclose Personal Data if it believes in good faith that such disclosure is appropriate (a) in connection with any legal investigation or proceeding; (b) to comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on MeUndies; (c) to protect or defend the rights or property of MeUndies, its Affiliates or its users; and/or (d) to investigate or assist in preventing any violation or potential violation of the law, this Privacy Policy, or our Terms of Service. 

  5. ###  Disclosure to Third Party Companies 

We may enter into agreements with companies that provide our Services by way of a co-branded or private-labeled website or companies that offer their products and/or services on our website ("Third Party Companies"). A Third Party Company may want access to Personal Data that we collect from its customers. As a result, we may disclose your Personal Data to a Third Party Company; however, we will not disclose your Personal Data to any Third Party Company for the Third Party Company's own direct marketing purposes, unless you have "optedin" by following the instructions we provide to allow such disclosure. If you have optedin to receive e-mail communications from a Third Party Company and later wish to discontinue receipt of these e-mails, please contact the Third Party Company directly to update your preferences. The privacy policies of these Third Party Companies may apply to the use and disclosure of your Personal Data that we collect and disclose to such Third Party Companies. Because we do not control the privacy practices of our Third Party Companies, you should read and understand their privacy policies.] Notice to California residents – your California privacy rights California residents who have provided personal data to MeUndies may request information about whether we have disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. In general, if we have made such a disclosure of personal data, upon receipt of a request by a California customer, we are required to provide a list of all third parties to whom personal data was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of personal data that were disclosed. California customers may request further information about our compliance with this law by e-mailing [support@meundies.com](mailto:support@meundies.com). Please note that we are required to respond to one request per California customer each year and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this e-mail address. 

##  8\. Third-Party Payment Processing. 

For online payments using credit, debit, Apple Pay, PayPal, Venmo and/or Automated Clearing House (ACH) payouts, we use the payment services of Stripe ([https://stripe.com](https://stripe.com/)) and Braintree Payments ([https://www.braintreepayments.com"](https://www.braintreepayments.com/)). To simplify the ordering process for you on your next order, we save the last four digits of your credit card, the expiration date of your credit card, the credit card type, your first and last name, your shipping and billing address, and a token identifier to match your information to your full credit card number, which is stored by our payment services. We do not store your full credit card number or your CVV2 number (the 3 to 4 digit security code on your card). We do not have access to your full credit card number, PayPal, Venmo or Apple Pay data stored by Stripe or Braintree Payments. For more information on how payments are handled, and to understand the data security and privacy protections afforded to such information, please refer to https://stripe.com/us/privacy and https://www.braintreepayments.com/legal

##  9\. Third-Party Websites. 

Our Site may contain links to third-party websites. When you click on a link to any other website or location, you will leave our Site and go to another site, and another entity may collect Personal Data or Anonymous Data from you. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for, these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites, or to any collection of your Personal Data after you click on links to such outside websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of every website you visit. The links to third-party websites or locations are for your convenience and do not signify our endorsement of such third parties or their products, content or services. 

##  10\. Your Choices Regarding Information. 

You have several choices regarding the use of information on our Service: 

  1. ###  Email Communications. 

We may periodically send you free newsletters and e-mails that directly promote the use of our Site, products, or Services. When you receive newsletters or promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications from us and you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail you receive or by contacting us directly (please see contact information above). Despite your indicated preferences for commercial e-mail messages, we may continue to send you account or service-related communications, including notices of any updates to our Terms of Service or Privacy Policy. 

  2. ###  Cookies. 

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to accept Cookies for any of the purposes described above, you can instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting Cookies or to prompt you before accepting a Cookie from the websites you visit. Consult your browser’s technical information. If you do not accept Cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the Services. If you have any questions about how to disable or modify Cookies, please let us know at the contact information provided above. 

  3. ###  De-Linking SNS. 

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to have your SNS account linked to your Account, please refer to the privacy settings of the SNS to determine how you may adjust our permissions and manage the interactivity between our Services and your social media account. 

  4. ###  Changing or Deleting Your Personal Data. 

Except for payment information, you may change any of your Personal Data stored in your Account by editing your Personal Data within your Account or by sending an e-mail to us at [support@meundies.com](mailto:support@meundies.com) Payment information stored by MeUndies as described in Section 8 cannot be edited. If you wish to edit such payment information, you will need to delete the payment information and add new payment information. Payment information may only be deleted if you do not have an active subscription at the time you submit a deletion request. When you request deletion of your Personal Data by us, we will remove the display of such Personal Data so that you will no longer see such data in your Account. However, we may retain your information for record keeping, auditing, fraud prevention, and similar purposes. 

  5. ###  Text Message Communications. 

You may agree to receive text messages regarding product offers and promotions by MeUndies via automated technology. You are not required to agree to receive text messages to make a purchase. You may, at any time, decide to stop receiving text messages regarding product offers and promotions by MeUndies by replying STOP to any text message you receive from MeUndies. If you need help or assistance with the messages, you may text HELP or call (888) 552-6775. So long as you agree to receive text messages, you will receive messages periodically and generally around four (4) messages per month. MSG and data rates may apply. Carriers are not liable for delayed or undelivered messages. 

##  11\. Changes to This Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy at [www.meundies.com](https://www.meundies.com/) and we will change the "Last Updated" date above. You should consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.
